<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Prices>

<Price id="1">
<name>What is WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>WinMaWeb is a social network dedicated to redistributing wealth back to the people.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="2">
<name>How can WinMaWeb benefit me?</name>
<description>WinMaWeb can benefit members in many ways
A) New members gain immediate access to great deals and can begin saving money.

B) Members who have built up their own social network will receive an income from their 5th tier of WinMaWeb members.

C) Members can become Agents by bringing in local businesses (Deals) to WinMaWeb and . Agents will receive an income each time one of those deals is sold on WinMaWeb.

D) Merchants may join free and benefit from the WinMaWeb membership and free advertising on their products and services.

Summary: Members are offered great deals from local businesses and can begin by saving a lot of money, members who built a network earn an income from their 5th tier, and members (agents) who recruit local businesses also earn an income.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>
<Price id="3">
<name>Does it cost anything to join?</name>
<description>No, WinMaWeb is free and always will be. It will never require a financial investment from you of your hard earned money. There will never be quotas on selling, nor buying*, nor recruiting. No enrollment fees, no montly fees.
        
For example: You may join for free and decide to never buy anything through WinMaWeb (but once you see the great deals being offered we doubt that this will happen :-) ! )

*There is only one exception to this rule:

The only time that members are required to spend money on WinMaWeb is after they have earned an income through WinMaWeb. At that point, WinMaWeb asks members to put 20% of their WinMaWeb earnings back into the network. The other 80% can be withdrawn directly and transferred to the member's bank account.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price> 

<Price id="4">
<name>How will members be asked to put money earned back into the network?</name>
<description>After you have earned money through WinMaWeb we will ask that you to spend 20% of that income on WinMaWeb deals. This requirement is there to strengthen the 'inner economy' of WinMaWeb and thus to attract even more businesses to the network. The other 80% of the money you earned is yours to withdraw freely and spend as you wish.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>
    
<Price id="5">
<name>Why would businesses offer great deals through WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>Businesses receive free marketing and publicity by offering deals on WinMaWeb. The exposure they receive is greater than any traditional advertising campaign. Businesses end up saving money by having to spend less on marketing and advertising, so they are able to offer their products and services at a much reduced cost to you, our WinMaWeb members.

Businesses are also never asked to buy in to WinMaWeb. Like you, businesses join for free.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>       
<Price id="6"><name>How can I refer my friends to WinMaWeb and begin growing my own social network?</name>
<description>Every member will receive a Referral ID. Give that Referral ID to your friends, post it on your wall in Facebook, etc., so that when they sign up they become your first network tier of WinMaWeb members</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="7">
<name>What if my friend forgets my Referral ID and signs up on WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>WinMaWeb will not allow new members to sign up without a Referral ID. If your friend tries to sign up and has forgotten your Referral ID he or she will most likely be contacting you so please keep your Referral ID handy.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>  

<Price id="8">
<name>What if someone signs up on WinMaWeb because they saw the comment on my Facebook wall or a similar electronic link?</name>
<description>WinMaWeb is designed so that your Referral ID is embedded in all links to the membership registration page. However, please post your Referral ID in the links just in case something goes wrong.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>  

<Price id="9">
<name>How will I know of the great deals being offered through WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>Once you sign up for a free membership you will have become a lifetime member. You will then be able to choose how you wish to be informed of the deals. You may subscribe, or unsubscribe, from E-mail notifications, you may login to the website and browse through a detailed listing of deals. In addition you may set up the WinMaWeb website to alert your smart phone of new deals as they are posted on the website.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price> 

<Price id="10">
<name>How can I buy a deal through WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>First, you must be a member. To become a member is free and quite easy, you don't even need a credit card.

Then, once you are a member, there are several ways to buy deals on WinMaWeb.

A) You can transfer money to your My Wallet (eg via PayPal or other means) and use that money to then buy deals through WinMaWeb.

B) Alternatively, you could use your credit card to buy deals without transferring any money.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="11">
<name>Why is WinMaWeb better than other social networks?</name>
<description>In two words: Transparency and Profitability. WinMaWeb is both more transparent and more profitable to members than all other social networks.

Members can see at any time exactly how their social network of friends and colleagues is building up. Members can see immediately how new businesses offer deals through WinMaWeb. And WinMaWeb is set up and built around the principle to redistribute wealth back to the people, so the percentages, savings and earnings equally favor the members at ANY tier level, and not just those who joined and started early.

Eg. The founders of WinMaWeb and those who joined early on will ONLY receive an income from their 5th Tier of members. Not from the 6th, 7th or 50th tiers as well. So a member who signed up on the 34th tier will receive an income from their 5th tier (the 39th tier of friends and colleagues), just like the original members who started on the 1st tier and only earn an income from the 6th tier members of their friends and colleagues.

In addition, WinMaWeb offers the members (agents) who bring in and recruit businesses an equal share of the profits from that business. This is to guarantee new members and businesses a clear and fair transparency as well as an increased profitability.</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>
    
<Price id="12">
<name>Why do I have to wait for the 5th tier of members before I earn an income from WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>
WinMaweb is not a Multi Level Marketing Company where only the early members benefit the most, instead we are a Uni Level Marketing Company where activity and commitment will determine how much a member earns. A member may join late and still develop a larger network than the founder. IN that case, the member will literally earn more money from the network than the founder (because members only earn money from their 5th tier, regardless of where they are in the whole network.)

But there is a simpler answer to that question: Because you will earn more, a lot more, that way.

Imagine this scenario: You network and tell all of your friends and colleagues and contacts about WinMaWeb and as a result ten of them become ;active; networkers in your first tier. Those ten people in your first tier do the same and tell all of their contacts about WinMaWeb and as a result each of them gets ten active networkers in their first tier (all of them together means 100 active networkers in your second tier). Following this model you will have 100,000 active networkers in your 5th tier (but only 10,000 in your 4th Tier and 1,000 in your third tier). Your WinMaWeb network income will be generated from the purchases made by everyone in your 5th Tier (not just the 100,000 active networking members, but all the other inactive members as well who are just taking advantage of the deals...)

Following this model, if every active networking member spends 10 dollars on WinMaWeb products and services, then you could expect an income of about 100,000 dollars from your 5th tier of active members (and much much more if you consider the purchases made by inactive members)	
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="13">
<name>How can I withdraw my money from WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>
Your member account has a My Wallet and a WinMaWeb Account. All the money in your My Wallet may be transferred at any time directly to your bank account or Paypal. Money from your WinMaWeb Account is moved automatically to your wallet after you have made a WinMaWeb purchase.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="14">
<name>How is money moved from my WinMaWeb Account to My Wallet?</name>
<description>
Once you make a WinMaWeb purchase an amount of money four times your purchase amount is automatically moved to your My Wallet. Eg. If you make a WinMaWeb purchase from your WinMaweb Account for 20 dollars then 80 dollars will automatically be moved to your My Wallet.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="15">
<name>What if I only have 30 dollars in my WinMaWeb Account and I make that WinMaWeb purchase for 20 dollars?</name>
<description>
Then the remaining 10 dollars in your WinMaWeb Account will automatically be moved to your My Wallet, and the next 70 dollars deposited into your WinMaWeb Account also be automatically moved to your My Wallet later. In effect, your WinMaWeb purchases will always be credited to your WinMaWeb Account for later.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="16">
<name>What countries are WinMaWeb in?</name>
<description>
WinMaWeb was founded in Singapore, but as the membership expands it will quickly become a global social network. Plans are already in motion to open WinMaWeb in the USA, Europe as well as in other Asian countries. Contact us if you'd like to help open your nation.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="17">
<name>What if I want to do more for the company than just being a WinMaWeb member?</name>
<description>
WinMaWeb is always looking for leaders in the community who may assist the network marketing company in opening new countries and assisting in other related areas such as legalization, marketing and network management. Contact us if you think your skills and talents could even further benefit WinMaWeb.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="18">
<name>Why is WinMaWeb better than other Social Networks for Merchants?</name>
<description>
WinMaWeb is better than other social networks because we take care of our members better. WinMaWeb members benefit from a better transparency and more profitability than what other social networks offer. These benefits to the members are directly transferred to the merchants because WinMaWeb will have more members, more members means more market exposure to Merchants, and more deals purchased.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="19">
<name>What if I lose my Voucher?</name>
<description>
Don't worry, if you lose your Voucher you may download it and print it out again . Each Voucher has a unique code that the Merchant will verify when you redeem it. Once that Voucher code has been used the Voucher is then consumed and no longer valid. (please see Terms and Conditions)
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="20">
<name>What if I want a refund?</name>
<description>
After you purchase a voucher you may automatically refund it within 7 days after the initial purchase, provided you have not used the voucher. If you have used the voucher you may still attempt to refund it, and WinMaWeb will contact the Merchant and discuss your case with them before deciding on the refund. To Refund a Voucher all you must do is send in a message to customer support (via the Contact Us button on any main page) and provide us with your Voucher Code and the details and reasons for the refund.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="21">
<name>What if someone steals my Voucher?</name>
<description>
Vouchers are like cash (please don't leave them laying around in a drawer or on your computer desktop). But, if someone steals your Voucher then your first steps should be:
1) contact the Merchant and let them know a thief is on the way (the Voucher has your name and contact info on it, so their crime will also include identity theft which is a felony in most countries...)
2) report the theft to the police.

Then let the Merchant and the Police do their jobs and bust the dumb thief. Then please contact us and we will report in our newsletter how WinMaWeb vouchers are safer than cash at helping to stop crime :-)
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="22">
<name>How can I bring a Merchant to WinMaWeb? - How can I earn Agent Commissions? - How can I become an Agent and post a deal on WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>
Please click this hyperlink to watch our tutorial movie on how to be an Agent.

If you want to earn more with WinMaWeb and wish to earn Agent Commissions on each purchase of a deal (then you earn 20% of the WinMaweb share) then you may contact Merchants and bring a Deal Offer in to WinMaWeb.

The first step is to click the ;Merchant Contract; button on the main menu of the website and then follow the steps to get the contract, and then go find a Merchant. Do you have friends that own businesses? Is there a local business near you that might have a lack of customers on Tuesdays? A store with too many size 38 shoes? A restaurant with the best food but not enough publicity? A dance school or TaeKwonDo studio that has too few students in their classes? Any local product or service provider may become a Merchant with WinMaWeb. Once you have found a Merchant you contact them and bring them the contract and introduce them to WinMaWeb.

The second step is to get the Merchant to become a member, if they are not one already (don't forget to use your Referral ID and develop your network at the same time!) and to fill out the Merchant Contract together. Once the deal has been set up then you contact WinMaWeb (link for contact us here) and we verify the contract details. You (the Agent), the Merchant, and a Witness sign and date the contract and then send it/bring it in to WinMaWeb (link to address).

The third Step is WinMaWeb verifies and validates the contract, WinMaWeb conducts a Verification and Test Transaction on the Agent and Merchant (this is a small payment of less than 1 dollar.) Once that verification is complete WinMaWeb upgrades the Member to an Agent. Agents (and Merchants) have an extra function on the Website- a new menu item appears ;My Offers; under which they may Add Offers to WinMaWeb.

The fourth Step: The Agent posts the Deal Offer on WinMaWeb (click here to see video/tutorial how to post a Deal Offer).

The last step: WinMaWeb verifies the Deal Offer. Once the deal offer has been accepted the Deal is now on and WinMaWeb members may purchase it.

Then you, the Agent, watch the deal sell, every sale turns into an Agent Commission of 20% of the WinMaWeb share... and the Agent earns money! Every time the merchant redeems a voucher, the agent earns their commission. Agents can review their income directly under the Transactions: Received Transactions Section on the main menu.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="23">
<name>What if a Merchant wishes to be his own Agent?
What if a Merchant wishes to post his own Deal on WinMaWeb?</name>
<description>
WinMaWeb requires that all members (merchants too) be referred by another member. Thus initially, most Merchants will be referred by Agents who are seeking to earn an income through Agent Commissions. However, later, once a Merchant is verified and already had a deal run on WinMaWeb, then the Merchant may post their own deals (and thus earn their own Agent Commissions.)
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>

<Price id="24">
<name>How does a Merchant get paid?</name>
<description>
Merchants have extra functions on the website that are not available to Agents or regular Members. One of those functions is to ;Cash In Vouchers; under Transactions.
Merchants will Cash In Vouchers once they have been redeemed by members. Once a Voucher has been redeemed by the Merchant through the website the money will automatically be deposited into the Merchant's My Wallet from which they may transfer the money as they wish.
</description>
<web>www.winmaweb.com</web>
</Price>
 
</Prices>